{
    "id": "edbfd366375640bd8af932a71d170343",
    "title": "First Conditional Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If I see Jennie, I …………………………. her your love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will give",
                "would give",
                "would have given"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "940bc163349a49c19259a715299ccc0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Oil ………………………. if you pour it on water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "floats",
                "will float",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3a5be37669d146b88250ec10fd4c23b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she …………………………….. to us, then we will have to go and see her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't come",
                "couldn't come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22366dc416944cd099e1f2f3887627e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………………… to learn a second language, you have to work hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wanted",
                "had wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0395e9bec3754747b4646ebcb6879d25"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you eat too much, you ………………………… fat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "would get",
                "would have gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed08ded2b5c743a0a9b9b076beefc3d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I know her name, I …………………………. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will tell",
                "would tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a14b65887fb0410ea02557c15dd3e7f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be absolutely happy, if I …………………………… a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ec82714b3234271869dd27ce4169818"
        },
        {
            "question": "What will you do, if you ………………….. your job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "lost",
                "had lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7669a4d85ff244ef88f7dce02f0d2fec"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we ……………………… a map, we will be able to get out of here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "287a5d0b94994ddaaae09936fa39ea4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will get up earlier if there ……………………….. a good reason to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b970e4b6c49743d2a1eaf88b0e03bc91"
        }
    ]
}